fieldnation.com 2014-02-28

# Privacy Policy

**Thank you for visiting fieldnation.com, a FieldNation, LLC site (the "Web Site"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on this Web Site.**

**Information Collection**

If you buy or sell services using our Web Site, we collect and store information that specifically identifies you or your account ("Personally Identifiable Information"). The Personally Identifiable information that may be collected includes: contact data (such as, name, mailing and email address, telephone number, cell phone carrier, and fax number), demographic information (such as, ZIP code, age, date of birth, and gender), and work-related data (such as, technical experience, skill sets, certifications, or job history). We may, in the future, include other optional requests for information from you, to help us to tailor the Web Site by delivering more personalized information to you. We may supplement our information with additional information purchased from third parties for marketing purposes. 

In order to access some services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password (your "Account"). As part of creating your Account, you may also be requested to provide questions and secret answers, which we use to help verify your identity and assist in resetting your password, as well as an alternate email address. Some services may require added security, and in these cases, you may be asked to create an additional security key. Finally, a unique ID number will be assigned to your Account.

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our services. We may also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses.

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for services and programs offered by us, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other services, programs and products that we believe may be of interest to you.

If you register as a provider, our third party customers and their representatives do have access to your personal information and you may also receive job emails, sms or phone calls directly from them. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as when we make changes to our database, to fulfill a request by you, or to contact you about your account with us. 

We sometimes use the non-Personally Identifiable Information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Web Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Web Site usage, as well as to offer you services, programs or products.

We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

Agents, affiliates and customers of FieldNation, LLC who have access to your Personally Identifiable Information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to recruit providers and engage their services. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that Personally Identifiable Information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information if disclosure is necessary to (i) comply with a court order or other legal process, (ii) protect our rights and property or that of our licensors, or (iii) enforce our other contractual rights.

Our advertisers may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you, if you provide such information to them. We do not send any of your Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers. You may see a cookie from a third-party banner server, and this cookie comes from the third-party banner server, not FieldNation, LLC. 

**HIPAA Compliance**

Field Nation meets and exceeds Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), as well as other national security requirements. Our secure website operates on a 256 bit encrypted Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and unique login and passwords are required for system access. This assures that your data is only accessed by authorized personnel. The system and uploaded data and attachments are stored and continually backed-up on 100% HIPAA secure servers with many redundancies. Please contact our staff for any specific questions about Field Nation's HIPAA compliance policies and procedures. 

**Cookies**

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, the Web Site uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our Web Site are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other Personally Identifiable Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the Web Site with Personally Identifiable Information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our Web Site, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We also may use cookies to offer you services, programs or products.

As is true of most web sites, we may gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We may use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Web Site, to track users movements around the Web Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

When visiting our Web Site, we may track the referring URL (the web page you left before coming to the Web Site) and the pages, links, and graphics of fieldnation.com you visited. This allows us to compile aggregate statistics about usage of our Web Site and allows us to gauge the popularity and effectiveness of specific web pages and any promotional programs we may be running. This information may be gathered globally and is not personally identifiable.

**Terms Specifically Applicable to Service Providers**

As part of registration as a provider, you must set up your Account by describing your experience, rates and qualifications, work profile, and schedule. Some of the information requested in the on-line registration is mandatory. If you decide to offer your services through our Web Site, potential third party customers will look to your Account to help them decide whether to make use of your services. Our customers will not be able to select you as a service provider, however, until you have agreed to our online contractor terms. 

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

For instructions on how you can access the Personally Identifiable Information that this Web Site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please [click here](mailto:support@fieldnation.com).

To protect your privacy and security, we will take commercially reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this online Privacy Statement or its implementation you may contact us by [clicking here](mailto:support@fieldnation.com).

**Other Limits to Your Privacy -- Third Party Sites**

The Web Site may eventually contain links to other third party web sites. Neither FieldNation, LLC nor its licensors are responsible for the content of these third party sites or their privacy policies. Please understand that any information that is disclosed on these sites becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

FieldNation, LLC reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Privacy Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of this statement. It is your responsibility to check periodically for changes.
